var questions = [{
    "question": "How many compartments does a cow’s stomach have?",
    "option1": "Three",
    "option2": "Four",
    "option3": "Six",
    "option4": "One",
    "answer": "2"
}, {
        "question": "Which is the largest mammal in the world?",
        "option1": "The hippopotamus",
        "option2": "The giraffe",
        "option3": "The blue whale",
        "option4": "The bison",
        "answer": "3"
}, {
        "question": "Which bird has the largest wingspan of any living bird?",
        "option1": "The wandering albatross",
        "option2": "The andrean condor",
        "option3": "The dalmatian pelican",
        "option4": "The emporer penguin",
        "answer": "2"
}, {
        "question": "Which is the fastest land animal?",
        "option1": "The cheetah",
        "option2": "The greyhound",
        "option3": "The lion",
        "option4": "The pronghorn",
        "answer": "1"
}, {
        "question": "What type of animal is a Mexican hairless?",
        "option1": "A cat",
        "option2": "A bat",
        "option3": "A hog",
        "option4": "A dog",
        "answer": "4"
}, {
        "question": "What kind of creature is a Portuguese man o’ war?",
        "option1": "A stingray",
        "option2": "A lizard",
        "option3": "A jellyfish",
        "option4": "A bird",
        "answer": "3"
}, {
        "question": "How many legs does a lobster have?",
        "option1": "10",
        "option2": "6",
        "option3": "4",
        "option4": "8",
        "answer": "1"
}, {
        "question": "What type of animal is a Flemish giant?",
        "option1": "A dog",
        "option2": "A rabbit",
        "option3": "A hamster",
        "option4": "A horse",
        "answer": "2"
}, {
        "question": "Which creatures produce gossamer?",
        "option1": "Mandrills",
        "option2": "Spiders",
        "option3": "Hummingbirds",
        "option4": "Rosemallows",
        "answer": "2"
}, {
        "question": "From which animal is mohair obtained?",
        "option1": "The angora rabbit",
        "option2": "The horse",
        "option3": "The angora goat",
        "option4": "The hairbrush",
        "answer": "3"
}, {
        "question": "Whereabouts do demersal fish live in the sea",
        "option1": "Near the top",
        "option2": "Near the middle",
        "option3": "Near the bottom",
        "option4": "These fish don't live in the sea",
        "answer": "3"
}, {
        "question": "How is the domestic cavy better known?",
        "option1": "As the guinea pig",
        "option2": "As the chinchilla",
        "option3": "As the hermit crab",
        "option4": "As the sugar glider",
        "answer": "1"
}, {
        "question": "How many bones does the giraffe have in its neck?",
        "option1": "14",
        "option2": "7",
        "option3": "12",
        "option4": "4",
        "answer": "2"
}, {
        "question": "A parliament is the name given to a group of which bird?",
        "option1": "The finch",
        "option2": "The parrot",
        "option3": "The swallow",
        "option4": "The owl",
        "answer": "4"
}, {
        "question": "Which is the largest living bird?",
        "option1": "The ostrich",
        "option2": "The albatross",
        "option3": "The bald eagle",
        "option4": "The king penguin",
        "answer": "2"
}]